Nail that sign firmly.
-Okay.
-And two more coats of paint on the sign.
Don't worry. I have enough paint.
-Apply a layer of wax on it.
-Mom.
They'll promote our Vacuum Chicken.
Already? I'm not ready yet.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Hello.
No worries, they'll gather some materials
and discuss tomorrow's shooting.
Are we having a meeting first?
Please, come inside.
-Okay.
-Thank you, ma'am.
We'll be counting on you
to promote us online.
Make sure to capture more close-ups
of the awards on our walls.
-Thank you.
-All right.
We'll shoot here.
Stand over there.
Everyone!
Zhuang Jie.
-Zhuang Jie is here.
Our store will be ready tomorrow.
Here, take these 20% off vouchers.
-Great.
-Thank you.
Come by anytime you want some chicken.
Whatever happens won't affect
Liaogen Chicken's quality and taste.
It's okay to call our family unlucky.
But the chicken
didn't do anything to anyone.
Nonsense. We're all neighbors.
No one will say such things.
That's right. Times have changed.
No one believes that nonsense.
Is every voucher 20% off?
-Then give me two.
-No problem.
Here you go. You can take three.
Thank you, everyone.
Our newly launched Vacuum Chicken
will be available next week
with a 50% discount.
Feel free to order
for your family and friends.
We'll cover delivery fees.
Help us spread the word.
-Okay!
-Thank you.
Good luck with your business.
What a great deal.
Let's buy a few more chickens.
ADAPTED FROM THE ORIGINAL WORK
"LOVER" BY SHE MU SI
UNDERSTANDING CHILDREN
Isn't it too late for you
to be reading these books?
Don't disturb me.
I just finished reading
about the dangers of rubber nipples.
This one is about potty training.
Maidong is already 30 years old.
You can't expect him
to start over on this.
Don't be ridiculous.
Fine.
Don't waste your energy.
Help me string these beads.
Or I won't be able
to get your gift done in time
for your birthday.
My birthday wish this year
is to read
all the educational books you have here
to find out
what went wrong when we raised Maidong.
Why is he so different from normal people?
You should read more books.
Otherwise, you'll just
keep talking nonsense.
Children are always normal.
It's your mindset that is wrong.
I'm the one who is wrong now, am I?
He's a young man in his thirties
without a girlfriend.
He goes to work and comes home.
Should he just stay single like a monk?
What's so good about marrying
and having children?
You're offending me too.
How can men and women be the same?
Women can live their whole lives
without men.
But men can't live without women.
Your argument has too many flaws.
If you say this online,
you'll definitely be bashed.
Is a lonely life easy?
By the time he gets to my age,
it'll be too late
for regrets.
And what good does it do you,
fussing and worrying so much?
Are you still
thinking of Zhuang Jie?
No.
I feel like a backseat driver.
All my efforts are futile.
That's right.
I smell something burnt.
Quick! Go get my medicine!
All right.
If you can create a new remedy
to cure Maidong's seriousness
so he can be
as lively and smart as others,
you can have the rest of my lifespan.
Thanks.
I can't figure out
that grandson of yours.
I can't do anything about it.
Beat him up.
-Slowly.
-All right.
Tie him up.
Don't make a sound.
-Hurry.
-I'm here.
Zhang Hongxu!
Chen Maidong.
Answer me.
Where is Zhang Hongxu?
He said he was tired
and wanted to experience
what it is like to be a parcel.
Get out!
Give a hand!
Come on.
Come here.
Chen Maidong!
This is all your fault!
Honey, we've been
slaving away half the night.
We wanted to have some fun.
Fun?
Chickens haven't been tagged and loaded.
And you want to play?
Honey,
don't be upset.
It's not good for conception.
I…
These chickens are driving me crazy.
They just keep coming.
The price was slashed so low.
I say we need to deal
with crafty merchants like Zhuang Jie.
What nonsense are you spouting now?
-Here.
-No, you…
I told you to read more books.
Did you?
If we're talking about crafty merchants,
no one can beat you two.
I finally have a night off
and you drag me here to work for free.
Now you're talking, are you?
It's fair for you to do some work.
That's right.
Did you think you could kiss Zhuang Jie
without consequences?
You're not getting out of this.
-Chen Maidong!
-Counterattack.
Sooner or later, I'll show Zhuang Jie
what kind of man you are.
You act like a decent guy in public.
But you're the worst of them all.
What did I do?
I know all those rotten ideas
were all yours.
My husband is a blockhead compared to you.
In the summer, you smashed watermelons,
splattering juice all over.
Did you ever clean the walls?
And in the winter,
you had icicle-eating contests
at the door.
Are you guys crazy?
Why didn't they fall and pierce you?
Okay, stop.
We'll leave, okay?
We're leaving.
Let's go.
Why are you laughing?
Go home to your wife and kids
and do something.
You keep hanging out here.
Is this a game room to you?
Go home if you have a wife.
The bachelor, you stay here.
We have tons of work to do.
Forget it.
He can't even get a wife.
What good is he for?
Even you are better.
How can he compare to me?
Hey, bachelor,
I'm going back to my wife too.
It's the hierarchy.
Just accept it.
Earlier, I mainly shared with everyone
about the popularity model.
That is,
how to use popularity
to increase your authority
and generate traffic.
This is the foundation of e-commerce.
The requirements are quite high.
That's all for today.
All right. Please take notes.
Work hard.
That's all. Goodbye.
Jie,
all the other sellers
have printed shipping labels.
No one handwrites the labels
like us anymore!
DELIVERY DETAILS
The equipment isn't here yet.
Just do it for two more days.
Then why did you
still sell hundreds of chickens?
Isn't that a good thing?
It means online business is worth doing.
They haven't even
formally promoted us yet.
A brief mention in a live stream,
and we get tons of orders.
Zhuang Jie, at this rate,
I think we should expand the factory.
My goodness,
my hands are going to fall off.
He Niaoniao, you're getting paid.
Don't complain.
I didn't know it would be so much work.
It's only 50 cents apiece.
The pay is too low. I protest.
As long as you don't go on strike.
Name your terms.
Jie,
is Liaogen Chicken
getting an official account?
Of course.
Influencers can help us
attract traffic in the initial stage.
We'll need our operations team
down the line.
Will someone be
in charge of the live streams?
We'll have to hire professionals.
Either way, it won't be you.
You're still a child.
Get back to work.
l know.
But I know our business best.
I can help with the planning at least.
No.
You're young.
Stop aiming for the limelight.
See, Jie?
Mom always discourages me.
I'll never grow up to be anything.
Mom,
you should change that habit.
Continue your work.
Okay.
Grandma.
Chicken for breakfast again?
We've had it for days
in a row now. I'm sick of it.
Stop complaining when you get food.
Why don't you cook?
You didn't cook the chicken either.
I'm spending a little money
to help Jie and her family
through a rough patch.
Do you have a problem with that?
I wouldn't dare.
You're already a grown-up,
yet you do nothing every day.
This old lady has to do
everything for you. And you?
You complain whenever you open your mouth.
Let's eat. Come on, let's eat.
Chen Maidong,
something so huge happened
to the Zhuang family,
and you don't even care.
You could've bought something
and gone to see them.
The mother and daughter
not only kept the factory going,
but also expanded their business.
They're doing even better than before.
They held up the sky when it fell on them.
They're real heroines.
One in a million.
If anyone could marry a woman like Jie,
they ought to go light incense
at their ancestors' graves.
And you?
You wasted a good deck of cards
dealt to you.
Fine, I won't talk about it anymore.
Let's eat.
What business
did they expand into?
Something about a vacuum chamber.
Pretty advanced stuff.
Vacuum what?
You ask a lot of questions.
Vacuum Chicken.
And something about doing online business.
All that trendy stuff must be Jie's idea.
So is she not leaving?
You have a lot of questions.
Ask her yourself.
LIAOGEN CHICKEN
Hey, Zhuang Jie.
Ms. Lin, keep a close eye on things.
Besides hygiene standards,
safety in production is more important.
HANDWASHING AND SANITIZATION AREA
All right. You get busy.
I'll look at the live stream.
-Okay.
-All right. See you.
LIAOGEN CHICKEN
-You're here, Jie.
-Good work.
-Hey, Jie.
Everything is ready, Jie.
-Okay.
-Okay, let's get started.
Hi, everyone. Welcome to my live stream.
Today, I'm introducing
Liaogen Chicken.
LIAOGEN CHICKEN
One chicken liver.
Six pairs of chicken wings.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Your daughter is really something.
She's so capable.
She's all right.
What else can we do?
It's just us now.
Take care.
-I've paid.
-All right.
How is your leg?
Everyone in town
has seen you zooming around.
It's like you're teleporting.
I'm fine.
I drive an electric scooter.
You drive like you're flying.
That's not safe.
Maybe we should buy a used truck.
Neither of us has a driving license.
Zhuang Yan won't come back.
Who will drive it?
Keep it this way for now.
I'll make a few more trips.
Then we'll hire a delivery person.
Focus on live streams and shipping.
Who was the one who taught me,
"It's not just chicken we deliver
but the human touch"?
It's not the same
if we hire someone else to do it.
Doing this work reminds me of
the benefit of having a man around.
It's one thing if I don't have one,
but you won't find one either.
This conversation
is veering towards dangerous territory.
Let's not discuss this further. Stop now.
You'll work yourself to death.
This is nothing.
I consider it an exercise.
Wang Xixia even envies me.
She says I naturally have low body fat.
Speaking of Xixia,
people said a while ago
at the train station,
there was a fashionable girl
with Chen Maidong from the funeral parlor,
your classmate.
What about them?
They kissed passionately.
Kissed…
Kissed passionately?
Do you even know
what a passionate kiss is?
I do. Just hearing about it made me blush.
But they said the girl was very stylish.
And she works in a big city. Is it Xixia?
It's not her.
How do you know it's not her?
Have you heard about this too?
No, but…
She has been going
on arranged dates in Shanghai.
How could it be her?
Who could it be, then?
Chen Maidong looks
like a good, mature boy.
It's probably the girl who has no shame.
Why do you care?
They kissed. So what?
Don't talk behind someone's back.
Who is?
They brought it up, so I listened.
As if I like to spread this around.
Give me a hand.
I'll do it.
We're having hot pot again tonight.
Buy some spinach on your way back.
Can we have something else?
It's hot pot every day.
He Niaoniao is sick of it.
You get food. Don't complain.
I'm dog-tired.
Who has the time and energy to cook?
I wish I had a secret housekeeper.
Here, I'll handle that.
Okay.
Here you go.
I'm starving.
Let's have instant noodles.
-Sure.
Throw in a sausage.
And an egg.
Okay.
What's the matter?
Go wash up and come eat.
My goodness! Heavens!
Braised pork, shrimp, and fish!
-Xixia!
-Wang Xixia.
Are you the secret housekeeper?
-You're a lifesaver!
-You are!
It's a special occasion
when Xixia is back.
We must have a drink.
-Okay.
-Why didn't you tell me? You surprised me.
All right.
-You're going to drink with me tonight.
-No problem.
An entire spread of fatty foods.
What will you eat?
Are you crazy?
Who sticks to a diet when they're home?
Eat everything!
-Drink!
-What do I drink?
Soup.
-Here.
-Cheers!
-Cheers.
-Thank you.
You're not young anymore!
Don't knock it back!
I'm only 73.
A young lady.
Only 73?
I'm 84.
We'll go to Yama in due time.
Touch wood!
Fine.
You spoiled me.
No old lady
would celebrate their birthday like this.
What difference
does being an old lady make?
Some wrinkles won't make you worthless.
This is completely unnecessary.
I know very well
what is inside.
This thing looks erotic
in the dim light of the night.
Are you serious?
Is this really my lucky color?
I would never pull a prank on you.
We are Scorpios.
This is who we are.
Remember to wear it every day.
You might just get lucky.
I can't wear it, then.
Maidong can have it instead.
Our birthday is on the same day.
He is also a Scorpio.
If you have good luck,
your grandson will have it too.
You have a point.
If I do well in life,
it will do him some good.
Maidong has a tough life.
His parents failed him.
The divorce was a disaster.
It's no wonder
he was traumatized.
Goodness.
On your last birthday,
you said Maidong was getting depressed
because of Song Yi.
Now that they broke up,
you're blaming others.
She was responsible in some way.
Maidong didn't
meet the right one.
You are a year older now.
You're a mature old lady.
Stop complaining all the time.
Fine.
Come on.
Blow out the candle.
Time to make a wish.
Happy birthday!
Cut the cake.
Wait.
I need to use the toilet.
Everything here is nice.
But after sitting a while,
my legs hurt when I stand up.
-Be careful.
-Sit down.
Whenever I see these pictures,
the urge to use the toilet
gets even stronger.
You should steer clear
of what you shouldn't see.
Then you'll have ease of mind.
I don't get it.
Why must a man dress like this?
Xixia,
why are you suddenly on a break as well?
I thought you and Zhuang Jie
were the model employees.
A higher-up from France
dropped into our company.
He bosses us around.
He's annoying. It's better not to see him.
Yes.
We never put up
with mistreatment in any form.
Are you spending your New Year here?
My brother keeps pushing me to get a visa.
He wants me to go to Canada
to visit my nephew.
He's three and still hasn't met me.
What about your dad?
Are you and your brother
never going to see him again?
We only had our mom
and not our dad when we were kids.
Now our mom is gone.
I'll pretend he never existed.
Not all parents
deserve to be loved.
People have children
out of selfishness,
not good karma.
If the parents are good,
they can have some attention.
But if they are not worthy,
stay away from them.
They are bad luck.
Well said, Godmother.
Indeed. You're always full of surprises.
However,
you can still choose the right partner.
You need to plan for your future.
Oh no. Here she goes again.
She isn't wrong.
You need real efforts to find true love.
Don't just wait for one
to knock on your door.
That's not dignity but laziness.
Cheers.
Mom, don't fall for her fancy words.
She may look smart,
but she is hopeless when it comes to men.
Girls always complain after a blind date.
But her?
She is fine with all of her dates
and thinks she can marry them.
Xixia, that is not good.
You have no idea.
She ruined my chances
with all of my potential future husbands.
Last time, there was a guy in finance.
He claimed to be 175 cm tall,
but he had height-boosting insoles.
Don't height-shame the man.
It's all genetic.
What matters is the character.
Yes.
But Xixia,
his height
does affect the future generation.
I also met a guy who owns a cinema.
He never stopped talking.
He wouldn't shut up
throughout the entire meal.
Didn't that give you a headache?
A man shouldn't talk that much.
It's excessive.
Fine.
Months ago, I met a guy who is an artist.
He paints.
Never get an artist!
Don't bring another Zhuang Yan home.
It's misery.
Wang Xixia,
admit it.
You have bad taste.
But I think life can still go on anyway.
With love, we can make it work.
Don't be so sure.
Fate plays a big part in a relationship.
Yes.
But we can't be too picky.
Life is tough.
Life is so tough.
There is a female celebrity I like.
During an interview,
she was asked,
"What do you think of men?"
She replied,
"I don't."
She earned my respect instantly.
I don't think
I've met a lot of good men.
I have no idea how to pick.
True enough.
I've had two marriages
and a son.
I still think I know nothing about men.
Hello?
We are closed.
No more deliveries.
You are…
LIN BAOBAO VETERINARY CLINIC
Ms. Lin?
Mrs. Chen?
Welcome, Jie.
Sorry, the food went cold on the way.
You should heat it up.
It doesn't matter. It's for tomorrow.
Sorry for troubling you to make this trip.
How much is this?
It's on the house.
Mrs. Chen talks about you a lot.
You made us little cakes the other day.
We're even.
Jie, I ordered the food
so you could be here
to pick Mrs. Chen up
and send her home.
It's her birthday.
She had a little alcohol.
I can't let her walk home on her own.
Maidong is busy.
I had no choice
but to ask you for a favor.
Ms. Lin, if you ever need help,
don't place an order.
I am only one call away.
See? Jie is the finest girl around.
All right. I'll send her home.
Are you drunk?
No, not me. I'm not.
Call me if you need anything.
Mrs. Chen, happy birthday.
You should've told me.
I would've prepared a present.
I have no need for that.
All I need is to see you.
How much did you two drink?
Why do you care?
Exactly.
Mrs. Chen, is this a new bracelet?
It's pretty.
Ms. Lin gave this to me
as a birthday present.
She said this is my lucky color.
It looks nice.
Why didn't Chen Maidong
celebrate your birthday with you?
The better way to put it
is that I didn't
celebrate his birthday with him.
Do you have the same birthday?
What are the odds?
In the past,
we celebrated it together.
But for some reason,
I didn't even receive a call from him.
He's probably too busy.
So, I brought a piece of cake for him.
We'll finish it tomorrow.
I'll make it up to him.
Mrs. Chen, I'll deliver the cake.
It's his 30th birthday.
He has to at least have a piece of cake.
Do you mean it?
I entrusted her to you!
How did this happen?
I want my daughter back!
Mom!
She never stopped crying.
She was sick for a very long time!
Hu Liyan!
You're a heartless wretch!
What did you do?
Why would my sister abandon her kid
and take her own life?
I didn't force her to commit suicide!
Right? I have nothing
to gain from her death!
My daughter was only 36!
Had she not
met a good-for-nothing like you,
she would still be…
Mom!
-Mom!
-What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Beat him up!
Stop fighting!
-We'll call the police!
-Stop it!
Calm down! Stop fighting!
Hit him!
-Stop it!
-Beat him!
-Beat him up!
-Stop fighting!
-Stop!
-What are you doing?
Stop fighting!
Back off!
Stop it! Stop!
-What are you doing?
-Why are you here?
Wait! Are you out of your mind?
You were just standing!
You were tough in school!
Stay out of this. Go!
Stop it!
Calm down!
Only I get to hit women,
not the other way around.
Don't make me hurt you.
Cousin?
Why are you here?
You even brought some helpers.
I didn't know
you had a reputation in Nanping.
Watch your mouth.
Your wife just passed away.
Is this how you should behave?
Do you even have a heart?
Cousin.
I apologize on behalf of my cousin.
I can take it from here.
Stop his bleeding.
Don't stuff the nose.
Lower his head.
Put an ice pack on it.
Feng Xilun, handle it.
Everyone, calm down.
Why don't we sit and talk it over?
Has it been ten minutes?
You're suffocating me.
The bleeding stopped.
Get up. Your legs must be numb.
My legs are doing better than your brain.
I work here. What else could I do?
But I heard you threaten
to hit the hooligan.
Because he wanted to hit you.
Forget it.
If your grandma is right,
a little bleeding
might be your lucky color.
Nonsense.
Chen Maidong,
happy birthday.
I think I smooshed it earlier.
Don't you want this?
Thank you.
What for?
For the cake or for saving your neck?
Both.
Don't be smug.
Your grandma asked me
to deliver this cake.
I came on her behalf.
I should thank her.
And I wish her a happy birthday.
She is happy.
She had a drink and got a present.
Really?
I thought you were the drunk one.
Can you smell it?
Go away.
I'll pass out from the fumes.
If you faint,
it won't be because of the alcohol,
but because of my beautiful face.
I think you really are drunk.
People might think
you're here to stir up trouble.
You can put it that way.
Why else would I hit that guy
for you in my condition?
Yes, no one has ever done that.
Here, have some cake.
Make this trip worthwhile.
I can still taste blood. You eat it.
Take a bite.
-No.
-Eat it.
Who is this?
The woman who died is his mother.
She's in there.
The driver fell asleep.
Text me when you reach home.
Chen Maidong,
what present would you like?
It is your 30th birthday.
Well…
Buy me some clothes.
I'm needed here. I can't leave.
Can't you shop online?
No.
So be it.
You even asked for more than one.
You made quite a greedy wish.
I'll pay.
Sure.
I'll keep the change.
What do you want?
I'll send it to you later.
Sir?
Time to go.
Go inside.
It's cold out here.
Do you often get
this kind of trouble at work?
It's the first time in our town.
It's usually the elderly
who die of natural causes.
My last workplace
was worse.
How so?
Do you want to know?
It wouldn't hurt to know.
I had to sew a dismembered body
back together.
I went to horrible crime scenes.
The worst of them all
was a person who died in a basement.
It was summer.
The body was only found after two weeks.
I'm not looking down on your job.
But I am worried.
It's just like when people know
about my disability.
No matter how polite or tactful they are,
it still affects their perception.
People like me
are destined to suffer stigmas.
How did you get through it?
Turn the disadvantage into my advantage.
When I was a salesperson,
anyone who knew about my condition
would never give me attitude.
Impressive.
You're the one who told me.
"Even a crutch can be used as a weapon."
Why aren't you sleeping yet?
Why were you out so late?
I was talking to Chen Maidong.
What are you watching?
I found this in your watch history.
These people are incredible.
The first three episodes were thrilling.
There were highly-decomposed bodies
and bodies from accidents.
These morticians have to work days on end.
Their hazmat suits were drenched.
This job requires
great mental and physical strength.
It's not a job for the faint of heart.
It's sensible to think that.
Don't give me that look.
Your mom just interrogated me.
She wanted to know if I was the girl
who was smooching Chen Maidong
at the station.
What did you tell her?
I denied it, of course.
First of all,
I'm that fashionable.
Secondly,
I'm not that open.
Thirdly,
I would never go near him.
Someone would eat me alive for that.
Get lost.
Let's get to the point, Zhuang Jie.
Are you in love with Chen Maidong?
ONE KNEE-LENGTH COAT,
TWO CASHMERE SWEATERS,
ONE HOODIE, TEN PAIRS OF UNDERWEAR
HEIGHT, 185 CM, WEIGHT, 65 KG
What's this?
Are you two planning
to open a fashion store?
Don't be so nosy.
GREAT MAN
Ten pairs of underwear?
You sure aren't shy.
Are we close enough
that I can buy you underwear?
Underwear?
Listen to it.
GREAT MAN
I'm busy. Be serious.
Judging by his voice,
he is wearing a mask.
I guess it's another busy night.
Zhuang Jie,
you're hopeless.
It's not about me.
Chen Maidong is doing perfectly fine.
What do you mean?
Is he not into you?
I guess so.
At least he's not that into me.
He would've said something otherwise.
How else do you want him to put it?
He asked you to get him underwear.
So do you think he sees me as a woman?
Fair enough.
What's the problem with these men?
Never mind.
I'm going back to Shanghai anyway.
It would be troublesome
if we were in love.
I'll treat him
as a friend I can talk to.
Zhuang Jie.
I think
Ji Tong may not have moved on from you.
Forget it.
The best thing about me
is I know my own worth.
I mean it.
On the day I came back,
we had an unpleasant chat.
I told him you had a boyfriend.
And?
And I sent him the picture
of you and Chen Maidong kissing.
Are you serious?
I wanted to get back at him.
But I think he still cares about you.
It's not my concern.
Have you really moved on?
Why would I lie about it?
That's good to hear.
We are still unsure
of what we are looking for.
But at least we know what we should avoid.
Do you know? You're a silly fool.
Listen up.
I can tell the differences.
The guy from the last blind date
is totally someone I should avoid.
That's rare.
That man is in his thirties.
He claimed to be
from a family of TCM practitioners.
But he was so over the top.
He had a whole entourage
as if he were a big shot.
He reminded me of my dad.
And do you know what his name is?
Cui Ge.
Who calls themselves that?
I came across a post online.
Someone was called "Lightning Ball".
It's a real name.
Don't interrupt.
Do you know what the worst part was?
Halfway through the date,
he said he was into me.
He said my looks and elegance
reminded him of his ex-wife a lot.
Who says that kind of thing?
Unbelievable.
There are unspoken rules in blind dates.
He shouldn't go on blind dates
if he doesn't know the rules.
He said I looked like his ex-wife.
Well, he looked like my deadbeat dad.
I felt like punching him.
Had I been tougher,
I would've smashed my glass cup
in his face.
How did you get
such an annoying blind date?
I'm curious.
What's wrong with you now?
I'm speaking from my personal experiences.
Some men
are literally a different species.
True.
I wonder what went wrong
with their minds.
Lightning?
Ball!
Lightning Ball!
Cui…
-Cui Ge!
LIAOGEN CHICKEN
Hello?
Drive safely.
Don't overtake
the funeral parlor's vehicle.
Is that your workplace's vehicle?
I didn't notice.
It's okay.
I'll let it slide.
Don't insult me.
I didn't notice, but I'm not ignorant.
All right.
I'm hanging up.
Focus on driving.
Wait.
Is there a reason
I can't overtake your workplace's vehicle?
Is it bad luck?
Now you're being ignorant.
Well, enlighten me.
The vehicle is now empty.
But if we are working,
the deceased gets priority.
You should make way.
Sorry.
I'll keep this in mind.
You learn from mistakes.
That's a good habit.
So…
Aren't you leaving?
I'll leave.
But I have to settle things at home first.
Okay, bye.
That's rude.
Should I pull over?
Pull over? What for?
So you two can talk.
I can't believe what you just said.
I almost mistook you for Feng Xilun.
I can't stand it
when you don't speak your mind.
Get rid of this habit.
Chen Maidong,
can't you say everything in one go?
Ji Tong?
ALL ANIMALS IN THIS PROGRAM
WERE TREATED KINDLY